Griffin Clark

Kingston, ON, Canada • (506) 476-2939 • griffinclark10@gmail.com • LinkedIn • GitHub

OVERVIEW

Experienced engineering physics student with a strong background in software engineering, including full stack development and data analysis. Proficient in Python, PHP, Laravel, and SQL, with experience in JavaScript, React Native, and jQuery. Currently conducting research on cooperative perception for autonomous vehicles, with a focus on feature extraction and feature fusion using deep learning.

EDUCATION

QUEEN'S UNIVERSITY, Kingston, Ontario

Bachelor of Engineering Physics & Computing, September 2018- May 2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DEALSOURCING, Victoria, BC

Full Stack Engineer, May 2022 - May 2023

- Acted as technical lead for a small SaaS Startup, independently rewriting the back end of a website using PHP and updating the front-end structure using Laravel, HTML, CSS, AJAX, and jQuery.
- Developed a Python scraper that obtains and stores 10,000+ datapoints per day in an AWS database accessed using SQL.
- Utilized agile development techniques to effectively manage and coordinate multiple streams of work within the teams, ensuring timely and consistent progress towards project goals.
- Experienced in working with HTTP requests and implementing data pipelines for the website.

ALACRITY CANADA, Victoria, BC

Software Engineer Intern, January 2022 – May 2023

- Oversaw the technical and asset acquisition for a small Startup, including working with GitHub, AWS RDS, Stripe, Namecheap, and Heroku.
- Delivered weekly updates to the board on progress and demonstrated dedication to completing work in a timely manner.
- Served the mid-size company as an in-house technical consultant, often fixing bugs & domain issues, and implementing page redesigns using Wordpress, Hubspot, and Namecheap.

MCDONALD INSTITUTE, Remote (Kingston, ON)

Research and Outreach Fellow, May 2021 – September 2021

- Advanced research in dark matter through the **complex mathematical modelling** of stellar and galactic formations with the use of the Queen's **supercomputer server**.
- Quickly adapted to unfamiliar hydrodynamic modelling software such as GIZMO, yt and DICE.
- Leveraged python fluency to analyze data coming from the models, as well as teaching the language to high school students.

RELEVANT PROJECTS & RESEARCH

ENPH 455 THESIS, Kingston, ON

Cooperative Perception for Autonomous Vehicles, September 2022 – December 2022

- Conducting research on **cooperative perception** for autonomous vehicles, with a focus on feature extraction using the **PointPillar method** and vehicle to infrastructure feature fusion using deep learning on the DAIR-V2X dataset.
- Investigating the potential benefits and challenges of cooperative perception for autonomous vehicles and developing new methods and algorithms to improve the accuracy and reliability of this technology.

ENPH 454 CAPSTONE PROJECT, Kingston, ON

Queue Hop - AI Line Estimator, September 2022 - December 2022

- Built an IOS/Android app using JavaScript and React Native for a class capstone project.
- Trained a **point based deep learning model** to count the number of people in line at an engineering bar on campus and deliver line count and wait time estimates through the app.
- Integrated a Google Sheets API to transfer and display analyzed data from the model to the app for user accessibility.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES/FRAMEWORKS/OS

• Python, PHP, JavaScript, TypeScript, Swift, C++, Java, VHDL, Laravel, React, Linux, Unix, Ubuntu